<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Class-resources on Cindy Baldwin Books</title>
    <link>http://cindybaldwinbooks.com/class-resources/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Class-resources on Cindy Baldwin Books</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://cindybaldwinbooks.com/class-resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>No Matter the Distance Classroom Resources</title>
      <link>http://cindybaldwinbooks.com/class-resources/no-matter-the-distance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cindybaldwinbooks.com/class-resources/no-matter-the-distance/</guid>
      <description>Discussion Questions for No Matter the Distance (You can download a printable PDF copy of these discussion questions here!)
Aligned with Fifth Grade Common Core Standards for English Language Arts (RL5.1-5.7; L5.5.A)
At the beginning of the book, Penny’s teacher assigns them to write a poem about “What I Know About Myself.” Penny feels like she knows others in her life, such as her family and friends, better than she knows herself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stars of Whistling Ridge Classroom Resources</title>
      <link>http://cindybaldwinbooks.com/class-resources/the-stars-of-whistling-ridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cindybaldwinbooks.com/class-resources/the-stars-of-whistling-ridge/</guid>
      <description>Discussion Questions for The Stars of Whistling Ridge (You can download a printable PDF copy of these discussion questions here!)
More than anything in the world, Ivy wants a “forever home”—a place she can put down roots. Ivy’s willing to do a lot of things to get what she wants, even if some of those things might hurt her or or family. Have you ever wanted something so badly you were tempted to make unwise choices to get it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginners Welcome Classroom Resources</title>
      <link>http://cindybaldwinbooks.com/class-resources/beginners-welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cindybaldwinbooks.com/class-resources/beginners-welcome/</guid>
      <description>Discussion Questions for Beginners Welcome (You can download a printable PDF copy of these discussion questions here!)
After her daddy&amp;rsquo;s death, Annie Lee is determined to stay invisible because &amp;ldquo;invisible people couldn&amp;rsquo;t be seen, and people who couldn&amp;rsquo;t be seen couldn&amp;rsquo;t be hurt&amp;rdquo; (page 7). Do you agree with her? Have you ever had a time where you found yourself choosing invisibility over the possibility of getting hurt?
Throughout the book, Annie Lee carries a two-headed quarter that used to belong to her father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where the Watermelons Grow Classroom Resources</title>
      <link>http://cindybaldwinbooks.com/class-resources/where-the-watermelons-grow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cindybaldwinbooks.com/class-resources/where-the-watermelons-grow/</guid>
      <description>MG at Heart Where the Watermelons Grow was the featured book for our August 2018 edition of the Middle Grade at Heart Newsletter! You can download a PDF of the issue. This discussion guide, designed with classrooms in mind, features an exclusive interview, discussion questions, a recipe for honey-sweetened watermelon limeade, an activity, and a printable coloring page.
HarperCollins Teaching Guide You can find a downloadable PDF of the educator&amp;rsquo;s guide that HarperCollins created for Where the Watermelons Grow</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
